<resources>
    <string name="app_name">My City app</string>
    <string name="reccomendation">Reccomendation</string>
    <string name="details">Details</string>
    <string name="defualt_name">Default</string>
    <string name="category_1">Sights</string>
    <string name="category_2">Food place</string>
    <string name="category_3">Gym</string>
    <string name="category_4">Fun place</string>

    <string name="C1_Reccomendation1">Pugad</string>
    <string name="C1_Reccomendation2">Tapuacan River</string>
    <string name="C1_Reccomendation3">Kultura</string>
    <string name="C1_Reccomendation4">Ambangonan River</string>
    <string name="C1_Reccomendation5">Holy Family Parish Pugo</string>

    <string name="C1_Reccomendation1_text">PUGAD (bird\'s nest) is one of the recreation and adventure landmarks in Pugo. It is a picturesque site with 3 hectares of green forests, lush mountains, and a clean river. It is 300 meters away from Marcos Highway.</string>
    <string name="C1_Reccomendation2_text">Tapuacan River (also known as Pugo - Cleanest Inland River of the North, Region I) is located in Barangay Cares (the smallest/inlet town which is situated at the foot of the Santo Tomas mountains range and about an hour away from Baguio passing through the Aspiras, formerly Marcos Highway leading to the Ilocandia Region). The natural scenery is also a 1-hour ride from San Fernando City and around 4–5 hours drive from Manila.</string>
    <string name="C1_Reccomendation3_text">Pugo\'s Kultura Splash Wave is a prime resort[22] (Km. 21 Marcos Highway, Barangay Cares). It has attractions: Lap pool, Pool Kiddie, Dolphin pools, 4 Giant Slides with Dropzone, Water Factory, Aerial Zip Lines, Wall Climbing, Sky Walker.</string>
    <string name="C1_Reccomendation4_text">Ambangonan is a barangay in the municipality of Pugo, in the province of La Union. Its population as determined by the 2020 Census was 1,161. This represented 6.00% of the total population of Pugo.</string>
    <string name="C1_Reccomendation5_text">As of 2012, the 1909 Holy Family Parish Church of Pugo (canonically erected in 1909), celebrates its fiesta every Last Sunday of December. It is under the jurisdiction of the Roman Catholic Diocese of San Fernando de La Union (Dioecesis Ferdinandopolitana ab Unione, Suffragan of Lingayen – Dagupan, which was created on January 19, 1970, and erected on April 11, 1970, comprising the Civil Province of La Union, under the Titular, St. William the Hermit, February 10). The heritage church is under a diocese of the Latin Church of the Roman Catholic Church in the Philippines from the Archdiocese of Nueva Segovia. Its Parish Priest is Fr. Crispin N. Reyes.</string>

    <string name="C2_Reccomendation1">Kambak Resto and Grill</string>
    <string name="C2_Reccomendation2">Cafe in the Sky</string>
    <string name="C2_Reccomendation3">Inihaw Republic</string>
    <string name="C2_Reccomendation4">Soul Cafe</string>
    <string name="C2_Reccomendation5">Matutinas</string>
    <string name="C2_Reccomendation1_text">Mapapa kambak ka sa sarap!Superb food, especially the sinampalukang kambing. The fresh mango juice and halo-halo are a must try. The place is just along the Santo Tomas highway with enough parking space. The ambiance is good. Service is 4/5</string>
    <string name="C2_Reccomendation2_text">Coffe date? Sagot kita ! Kaya tara na at subukan ang Cafe in the Sky. Indulge a beautiful view habang nagkakape.</string>
    <string name="C2_Reccomendation3_text">Indulge in iconic flavors at Inihaw Repuplic. Savor crispy, finger-licking chicken that\'s a true culinary classic. From the original recipe to bold new creations, each bite is a burst of comfort and satisfaction. With a legacy spanning decades, Inihaw\'s signature taste and friendly ambiance invite friends and families to share memorable meals. Whether relishing the secret blend of herbs and spices or exploring a menu of delectable options, Inihaw Republic offers a timeless dining experience that brings people together over a shared love for delicious, crave-worthy food.</string>
    <string name="C2_Reccomendation4_text">Delight in warm ecstasy at Soul\'s Cafe. Experience artisanal creations that dance on your taste buds with a symphony of flavors and textures. From classic vanilla to innovative concoctions, Souls\'s crafts each cup with passion and precision. Indulge in creamy indulgence that sparks joy in every cup. Whether seeking a sweet escape on a warm day or a comforting treat year-round, Soul\'s Cafe promises a sensory journey that transcends ordinary desserts. </string>
    <string name="C2_Reccomendation5_text">Lutong Bahay at Matutinas Restaurant. Masarap na at mura pa, kaya ano pang hinihintay mo? Halina sa Matutinas Lutong Bahay!</string>

    <string name="C3_Reccomendation1">West Side Fitness Gym</string>
    <string name="C3_Reccomendation2">Star Fitness Gym</string>
    <string name="C3_Reccomendation1_text">Elevate your fitness journey at Flyefit. This cutting-edge gym offers a haven for wellness enthusiasts of all levels. With state-of-the-art equipment, dynamic classes, and 24/7 access, Flyefit empowers you to sculpt your body, boost your energy, and enhance your well-being on your terms. Whether you\'re a dedicated athlete or just starting your fitness path, the supportive atmosphere and expert trainers guide you toward your goals. Embrace a holistic approach to health and embrace a community that shares your dedication. Flyefit is more than a gym; it\'s a transformative space where you can redefine your limits and elevate your life.</string>
    <string name="C3_Reccomendation2_text">Discover the ultimate wellness haven at WestWood. This luxurious fitness and lifestyle destination redefines your wellness journey with world-class facilities and personalized services. Indulge in state-of-the-art fitness equipment, rejuvenating spa experiences, and an array of wellness classes designed to nurture your body and mind. Whether you\'re seeking to elevate your physical performance, unwind in serene surroundings, or connect with a community of like-minded individuals, WestWood offers an exclusive escape where health and relaxation intertwine. Embrace a holistic approach to well-being and embark on a transformative path that enriches every aspect of your life at WestWood.</string>

    <string name="C4_Reccomendation1">Bahay na Bato</string>
    <string name="C4_Reccomendation2">Bato De Luna</string>
    <string name="C4_Reccomendation3">Immuki Island</string>
    <string name="C4_Reccomendation4">Bauang Grape Farm</string>
    <string name="C4_Reccomendation1_text">Bahay na Bato, just like its name, is a house that is made entirely from pebbles and stones found on the pebble beach just beside it. It was built as a family rest house and later opened to the public in 2015 as an art gallery called Kamay Na Bato Art Gallery. The house features several wooden and stone sculptures by Bong Kim, a Korean artist.</string>
    <string name="C4_Reccomendation2_text">Bato de Luna is an art gallery located in Nalvo Norte, Luna, La Union. It showcases the works of Mr. Bong Kim, a Korean stone sculptor, and exhibits different art using stones and mural arts. Luna has a pebble-covered beach, and the gallery is built of stone. The grounds at Luna’s Bahay na Bato consist of large stone carvings such as hearts, flowers, animals, and funny characters.</string>
    <string name="C4_Reccomendation3_text">Immuki Island is a lagoon located in Brgy. Paraoir, Balaoan, La Union1. It is part of the Paraoir Beach and is a new tourist attraction. Immuki Island is not really an island but a series of pools and small lagoons formed by water entrapped between coral rocks. There are three lagoons at Immuki that are larger and deeper than at Currimao. Locals visit the island mainly for its three big lagoons that are perfect for swimming and cliff jumping.</string>
    <string name="C4_Reccomendation4_text">With decades of experience in grape farming, Bauang vineyard owners are now maximizing it to include grape picking to the delights of the visitors. Location Address: Bauang, La Union, Philippines</string>


    <string name="back_button">Back Button</string>
</resources>