<resources>
    <string name="app_name">My City app</string>
    <string name="reccomendation">Reccomendation</string>
    <string name="details">Details</string>
    <string name="defualt_name">Default</string>
    <string name="category_1">Sights</string>
    <string name="category_2">Food place</string>
    <string name="category_3">Gym</string>
    <string name="category_4">Fun place</string>

    <string name="C1_Reccomendation1">The Spire</string>
    <string name="C1_Reccomendation2">Botanic Gardens</string>
    <string name="C1_Reccomendation3">Portmanock Beach</string>
    <string name="C1_Reccomendation4">Bray Head Mountain</string>
    <string name="C1_Reccomendation5">St Patricks Church</string>

    <string name="C1_Reccomendation1_text">Discover breathtaking heights and architectural marvels at The Spire. Ascend this soaring pinnacle for an unparalleled panorama of the city\'s grandeur. A testament to human ambition, The Spire offers an immersive journey through its innovative design and historical significance. From its glass-framed elegance to its symbolic representation of progress, this iconic landmark stands as a must-visit destination. Experience urban beauty from a new perspective, where sky and city merge in an awe-inspiring display. Whether seeking inspiration or capturing memories, The Spire promises an unforgettable adventure into the heart of architectural wonder and urban allure.</string>
    <string name="C1_Reccomendation2_text">Immerse yourself in nature\'s splendor at the Botanic Gardens. A serene oasis of biodiversity and tranquility, it invites you to escape the urban bustle. Wander through lush landscapes, each corner a living tapestry of vibrant flora from around the world. Discover a peaceful refuge to rejuvenate your senses, where colors, scents, and textures harmonize in perfect balance. From educational trails to serene ponds, the Botanic Gardens offer a journey of wonder and serenity. Whether seeking respite or a deeper connection with the natural world, this verdant haven promises an enriching experience for all.</string>
    <string name="C1_Reccomendation3_text">Experience coastal paradise at Portmarnock Beach. With its golden sands and rolling waves, it\'s a haven for beach lovers and nature enthusiasts. Bask in the sun\'s embrace, indulge in invigorating swims, or stroll along the shoreline with the soothing sounds of the sea as your backdrop. The stunning vistas of the Irish Sea and the iconic Martello Tower create an unforgettable ambiance. Whether you seek solitude or lively beach activities, Portmarnock Beach offers a picturesque escape. Embrace the beauty of nature\'s simplicity and the joy of the ocean\'s embrace in this coastal gem.</string>
    <string name="C1_Reccomendation4_text">Embark on an exhilarating journey to Bray Head Mountain. Rising majestically above the coastal town, it promises breathtaking vistas and an invigorating hike. Traverse lush trails and rocky paths, each step revealing panoramic views of the Irish coastline that will steal your breath away. At the summit, catch your breath while gazing upon a sweeping panorama of land and sea, a reward for your determination. Bray Head Mountain offers a captivating blend of natural beauty and physical challenge, making it an ideal destination for adventure seekers and nature enthusiasts alike. Discover the thrill of conquering heights and savoring unparalleled vistas.</string>
    <string name="C1_Reccomendation5_text">Immerse yourself in history and spirituality at St. Patrick\'s Church. This architectural masterpiece stands as a testament to faith and artistic grandeur. Admire intricate stained glass windows that illuminate the interior with a kaleidoscope of colors, and marvel at the craftsmanship of its ornate decorations. Step into a tranquil sanctuary where the past and present merge in a place of reverence. Whether seeking solace, cultural insight, or awe-inspiring architecture, St. Patrick\'s Church offers a haven of serenity and a glimpse into the rich tapestry of heritage. Visit to experience the fusion of devotion and artistic brilliance in a sacred setting.</string>

    <string name="C2_Reccomendation1">Underground Indian Place</string>
    <string name="C2_Reccomendation2">Welcome City</string>
    <string name="C2_Reccomendation3">KFC</string>
    <string name="C2_Reccomendation4">Ginos</string>
    <string name="C2_Reccomendation5">Wings</string>
    <string name="C2_Reccomendation1_text">Embark on a sensory voyage to the Underground Indian Place. Venture beneath the surface to a realm of aromatic spices, vibrant colors, and authentic flavors. Experience the heart of India\'s culinary and cultural essence, as you indulge in a symphony of tastes that awaken your palate. Immerse yourself in an ambiance that transports you to bustling Indian streets, adorned with intricate decor and immersive storytelling. Whether you\'re a connoisseur of Indian cuisine or a curious explorer, this hidden gem offers an unforgettable passage to India\'s soul. Discover the magic of tradition and innovation woven seamlessly underground, creating an enchanting experience like no other.</string>
    <string name="C2_Reccomendation2_text">Step into a world of captivating diversity at Welcome City. This cultural hub beckons with open arms, embracing a rich tapestry of traditions, cuisines, and experiences. Wander through vibrant markets, where global flavors and local crafts intertwine. Immerse yourself in immersive exhibits that celebrate art, history, and innovation. From serene parks to bustling streets, Welcome City boasts an array of urban delights. Engage with welcoming locals and forge connections that transcend borders. Whether you\'re a curious traveler or a seeker of cross-cultural encounters, this city invites you to broaden your horizons and find familiarity in the unfamiliar. Explore a microcosm of our interconnected world and enrich your journey with boundless encounters.</string>
    <string name="C2_Reccomendation3_text">Indulge in iconic flavors at KFC. Savor crispy, finger-licking chicken that\'s a true culinary classic. From the original recipe to bold new creations, each bite is a burst of comfort and satisfaction. With a legacy spanning decades, KFC\'s signature taste and friendly ambiance invite friends and families to share memorable meals. Whether relishing the secret blend of herbs and spices or exploring a menu of delectable options, KFC offers a timeless dining experience that brings people together over a shared love for delicious, crave-worthy food.</string>
    <string name="C2_Reccomendation4_text">Delight in frozen ecstasy at Gino\'s Ice Cream. Experience artisanal creations that dance on your taste buds with a symphony of flavors and textures. From classic vanilla to innovative concoctions, Gino\'s crafts each scoop with passion and precision. Indulge in creamy indulgence that sparks joy in every spoonful. Whether seeking a sweet escape on a warm day or a comforting treat year-round, Gino\'s Ice Cream promises a sensory journey that transcends ordinary desserts. Embrace the artistry of frozen delights and make cherished memories with every luscious bite at this haven of frozen confections.</string>
    <string name="C2_Reccomendation5_text">Elevate your dining experience at Wings. Delight in a medley of succulent, saucy chicken wings that cater to every palate. From mild to fiery, each flavor profile is a tantalizing adventure. With a welcoming atmosphere and communal spirit, Wings is the ideal spot for friends and sports enthusiasts to gather and celebrate. Whether diving into a variety of dipping sauces or exploring unique wing creations, this destination promises a finger-licking journey through bold tastes and camaraderie. Discover the joy of messy, flavorful feasting that embodies the essence of comfort food, shared laughter, and unforgettable moments.</string>

    <string name="C3_Reccomendation1">Flyefit</string>
    <string name="C3_Reccomendation2">WestWood</string>
    <string name="C3_Reccomendation1_text">Elevate your fitness journey at Flyefit. This cutting-edge gym offers a haven for wellness enthusiasts of all levels. With state-of-the-art equipment, dynamic classes, and 24/7 access, Flyefit empowers you to sculpt your body, boost your energy, and enhance your well-being on your terms. Whether you\'re a dedicated athlete or just starting your fitness path, the supportive atmosphere and expert trainers guide you toward your goals. Embrace a holistic approach to health and embrace a community that shares your dedication. Flyefit is more than a gym; it\'s a transformative space where you can redefine your limits and elevate your life.</string>
    <string name="C3_Reccomendation2_text">Discover the ultimate wellness haven at WestWood. This luxurious fitness and lifestyle destination redefines your wellness journey with world-class facilities and personalized services. Indulge in state-of-the-art fitness equipment, rejuvenating spa experiences, and an array of wellness classes designed to nurture your body and mind. Whether you\'re seeking to elevate your physical performance, unwind in serene surroundings, or connect with a community of like-minded individuals, WestWood offers an exclusive escape where health and relaxation intertwine. Embrace a holistic approach to well-being and embark on a transformative path that enriches every aspect of your life at WestWood.</string>

    <string name="C4_Reccomendation1">Escape room</string>
    <string name="C4_Reccomendation2">Token</string>
    <string name="C4_Reccomendation3">Cineworld</string>
    <string name="C4_Reccomendation4">Ned Kellys</string>
    <string name="C4_Reccomendation1_text">Embark on an exhilarating adventure at the Escape Room. Immerse yourself in a real-life puzzle, where wit and teamwork are your keys to success. Uncover hidden clues, solve intricate riddles, and unravel mysteries in a race against time. From themed scenarios to immersive storytelling, the Escape Room promises an unforgettable experience that challenges your intellect and bonds with friends and family. Whether you\'re a puzzle enthusiast or a thrill-seeker, step into a world of intrigue and excitement, where every solved enigma brings you one step closer to freedom. Dare to unlock the thrill of the unknown and celebrate victory together.</string>
    <string name="C4_Reccomendation2_text">Experience a world of fun and nostalgia at Token. This vibrant arcade bar blends retro gaming with modern socializing. Play a variety of classic arcade games and pinball machines while sipping on craft drinks and savoring delectable bites. With its unique fusion of entertainment and culinary delights, Token is a haven for gamers, foodies, and those seeking a lively atmosphere. Whether you\'re reliving childhood memories or discovering vintage games for the first time, Token offers a unique blend of nostalgia, camaraderie, and excitement that keeps the good times rolling. Immerse yourself in a world where the past meets the present for an unforgettable night out.</string>
    <string name="C4_Reccomendation3_text">Dive into cinematic magic at Cineworld. Immerse yourself in the latest blockbusters and timeless classics on the big screen. With state-of-the-art technology and comfortable seating, Cineworld offers an unparalleled movie-watching experience. Whether you\'re a film buff seeking visual spectacle or a casual viewer looking for entertainment, this theater chain invites you to escape into captivating stories and stunning visuals. From epic adventures to heartfelt dramas, Cineworld brings stories to life in larger-than-life dimensions. Gather with friends, family, or solo to share the joy of cinema in an environment designed to transport you into the heart of storytelling.</string>
    <string name="C4_Reccomendation4_text">Immerse yourself in history and culture at Ned Kelly\'s. This iconic establishment pays homage to the legendary Australian outlaw and his era. With its rustic charm and authentic decor, Ned Kelly\'s offers a unique dining and entertainment experience. Indulge in hearty pub fare and local brews while surrounded by artifacts and memorabilia that tell the tale of the outlaw\'s life. Whether you\'re a history buff, a fan of Australian heritage, or simply looking for a cozy spot to enjoy good food and company, Ned Kelly\'s invites you to step back in time and relish the spirit of an era gone by.</string>

    <string name="back_button">Back Button</string>
</resources>